Guide to the Samuel Shaffer papers, 1948-1982 MS2091
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Chronological files, 1948-1976; MS2091 Series 1; 17 Linear feet
  - Chronological files, 02/1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Vietnam debate (2/2/66); Vietnam debate (2/3/66); Vietnam debate (2/4/66); David Bell testimony (2/4/66); Add to domestic legislation file (federal aid); LBJ's domestic program; Add to Vietnam debate file (2/4/66); Tax file (3/10/66); The tax bill and the Senate rebellion (3/10/66)
  - Chronological files, 03/1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Hartke (3/17/66); Congress Week (3/18/66); Correction (3/19/66) N14 Hartke; Query #3 (3/24/66) (Food for Freedom Program); Congress Week--triumph and rebellion (3/24/66)
  - Chronological files, 04/01/1966-04/15/1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Nation/Iselin from Shaffer (Drew Pearson) Dodd (4/1/66)--add to file of (3/31/66); (Pearson-Anderson) Congress Week (4/1/66) Population Control (4/5/66) Congress mood (4/7/66) Elliot/Diamond/Hudard from Shaffer (4/7/66); (Ken Woodward) Violin (4/14/66)(Grass Roots Soundings)
  - Chronological files, 04/16/1966-04/30/1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Dodd and ethics Nation, Foreign from Shaffer (Excerpt from the recently published hearings by the subcommittee on the Far East and the Pacific of the House Foreign Affairs); Nation, Iselin, Trippett from Shaffer (4/22/66); (Statement by Senate Ethics Committee) Reapportionment (4/22/66) Dodd (4/22/66) Nation, Iselin Trippett from Shaffer 4/22/66; (Announcement from Sen. Tom Dodd) News Release-Thomas J.Dodd; Congress Week-rent supplement, etc (4/28/66) Nation from Shaffer (4/29/66)(Congress Week file) (Humphrey); Query #10, 4/48/66 (4/29/66)(Ev Dirksen) CIA roundup story (4/28/66) Dodd (4/28/66) Dick Stout (in Nation) from Shaffer (4/29/66) (Dirksen); Dodd (add to file)--4/29/66 Dognapping (4/29/66)
  - Chronological files, 05/1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Money bills (5/5/66); Your guery #11, 5/5/66 (population explosion); Letters (Lorelle Alexander) from Washington/Shaffer (Letter of complaint from Whitaker and Baxter); Dirksen (5/12/66); Obscenity calls 5/12/66; Congress Week (5/19/66); Correction 5/20/66 (Biz is Housing); Your query #1 5/20/66 (Cellar-civil rights); Nation from Shaffer/Washington (update telephone obscenity story); Dirksen 5/27/66; Violin (Kuchel); Congress Week (5/27/66); Primaries (5/27/66); Nation from Shaffer May 28, 1966 (N16 Congress)
  - Chronological files, 06/1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Rabb from Shaffer (your query #10, 6/2/66)(Dawson); Congress (6/2/66); Add Congress file (6/3/66); Nation from Shaffer June 4 1966 (N13 Congress); Congress Week (6/16/66); Nation, Iselin from Shaffer (6/17/66) (Fulbright and; LBJ in Nation); Press from Shaffer (6/17/66)(Johnson) Auto Safety (6/23/66) Add to Auto Safety file Poverty Draft 6/23/66 "Arrogance of dissent" #24 Congress (6/30/66)
  - Chronological files, 07/1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Violin--Congress (7/14/66); Dodd (7/20/66); Congress; Civil Rights (7/28/66); CIA (7/29/66)
  - Chronological files, 08/1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Religion, Smith from Shaffer (School prayer hearings); August 3, 1966 Civil Rights (8/4/66); Religion, Smith from Shaffer Prayer (8/4/66) Airline strike (8/4/66); Nation from Shaffer August 6, 1966 (N22 New Violin) Correction Nation and Copy Desk (N13 Congress) No.15 8/11/66 Greene, Newsmakers from Stout; (Yarmolinsky) Congress Week (8/11/66) Congress Week (8/18/66) Violin (8/18/66); Nation, Goldman from Shaffer, Washington (Add to violin file 8/19/66) Science/Elfin, Nation, Martin from Shaffer; (Mohole Project 8/19/66) Nixon (8/25/66) Congress (8/25/66) Add Congress file (8/26/66)
  - Chronological files, 09/1966-10/1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week: the Kennedy-Johnson Confrontation; (10/3/66) Nation-Kosner Shaffer (Immediate reaction to LBJ's; cancellation of political swing (10/3/66) Iselin from Shaffer 10-12-64 (Appropriation) Bobby Kennedy (10/12/66) Demonstration Cities-and the congressional countdown; (10/13/66) Education, Russin, Shaffer, Washington Query #6; (10/17/66)(American Civil Liberties Union) Congress Roundup; For box with Congress roundup (10/20/66) USIA Prestige Polls (10/27/66) USIA Polls add file (10/27/66) Iselin from Shaffer (10/28/66)(LBJ) Correction Periscope and Copy Desk from Shaffer--; 10/29/66 (Prestige polls); 12.N - 12/1966 Congress fore cast (11/10/66); Nation from Shaffer (november 12, 1966)(N11 Congress) Newsmakers, Roeder Shaffer-? (Query #4 (12/1/66)-Powell Newsmakers Shaffer, Washington (Query #19 (12/1/66); (Dirksen) Violin (12/2/66); Douglass press Conference (12/8/66) Bob Christopher (special projects)Shaffer, Washington; (12/22/66)(Demonstration Cities); Mel from Sam-(12/22/66)(The Projected Cover Story) Nation, Iselin, Trippet from Shaffer (Powell) Nation, Iselin, Trippet from Shaffer (Powell) OOP Cover Story-"The Sword and the Oil can"(1/2/67)
  - Chronological files, 01/1967-09/1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Nation, Iselin, Goldman, Shaffer, Washington (1/4/66) with cover (Mansfield's comments on the 90th Congress; Nation, Iselin, Goldman, from Shaffer (1-4-67) (Add Cover file); Powell (1/5/67) - Take II; Nation, Iselin from Shaffer (1/5/67)(Republican legislative program); Add to cover file 1-3-67 (Dirksen); Correction (1/14/67)(N13 Congress); Correction (1/14/67)(N17 Violin); Nation and Copy Desk from Shaffer (N13 Congress); Congress (1/12/67); Filibuster fight (1/19/67); Add filibuster file (1/20/67); Iselin from Shaffer (1/20/67)(Powell); Correction (1/21/67)(N14 Senate blues); Consular Treaty (1/26/67); Add treaty file (12/7/67); Correction (2/4/67)(N15 treaty); Nation? Cannon from Shaffer (Aug 25 1967)(with cover) (LBJ)
  - Chronological files, 10/1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] GOP and Vietnam issue (Oct 5 1967); Add to Congress/Vietnam (Oct 6 1967); Congress Week (10/02/67)(Oct 12 1967); Add to Congress file (10/13/67)(Oct 13 1967); LBJ-Congress (The View from the Hill)(Oct 12 1967); Correction (10/4/67)(N18 Congress)(Oct 14 1967); Nation from Shaffer (10/14/67)(Oct 14 1967)(N20-Violin); Congress Week (10/19/67)(Oct 19 1967); Biz, Brink Shaffer Washington (to go with Spotlight; with Business Story (10/20/67)(Oct 10 1967); (Protectionist sentiment); Add to Congress file (10/20/67)(Oct 20 1967) Waters/Life and Leisure from Shaffer (10/21/67); (Hippie Cover) (Oct 20 1967) Ed Long (Oct 26 1967); Congress Week (10/26/67)(Oct 26 1967)(Bow) With Backlash cover (10/26/67) Correction (10/28/67)(N13 Long)
  - Chronological files, 11/1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week (11/2/67); Congress Week file (Nov 2 1967) (Redistricting) Add Congress (11/3/69) Congress Week (Nov 9 1967) Congress Week (10/16/67)(Nov 16 1967) Nation, Alpern from Shaffer (11/16/67)(Rosenthal) Business/Periscope from Shaffer (Nov 17 1967)(Trends) (Trade fairs)
  - Chronological files, 12/1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (12/7/67); Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (12/6/67)(Congress); Congress roundup (12/13/67); Nation, Iselin, Goldman, Shaffer, Washington (12/14/67); (Dirksen and Congress); Add to LBJ file (12-14-67); For the LBJ week (12/14/67); The shape of the congressional races (Dec 21 1967); To Goldman from Shaffer (Congress)(Dec 28 1967)
  - Chronological files, 01/1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (1/11/68)(Congress); Congress Week (1/18/68); Add to State of Union Box Score (Jan 19 1968); Congress and the "Pueblo" incident (Jan 25 1968); Add to Pueblo file (Jan 25 1968); Gardner Resignation-Congressional view (Jan 25 1968); Add to Pueblo file (Jan 26 1968)(1/26/68)
  - Chronological files, 02/1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Civil Rights (2/22/68); Morton (1/23/68)(Feb 23,1968); For the Violin (1/22/68)(Feb 23, 1968); Correction (2/24/68)(N15 Congress); Correction (2/24/68) (N20 Violin); Tonkin Gulf (1/25/68)(Jan 25 1968); Congress: Civil Rights, etc. (Feb 29, 1968); Add Congress Week-The Arts and Humanities Bill (Feb 29 1968); Add to Congress, civil rights (3/l/68(Mar 1 1968) Cover (Mar 1 1968)(Rockefeller)
  - Chronological files, 03/1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Congress: Civil Rights, etc., (3/7/68); McCarthy (3/7/68)(Mar.7 1968); Iselin/Nation from Shaffer (Mar 8 1968)(Gerald Ford); Massachusetts (Mar 8 1968); Add Congress: 1/8/68; Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Gold 3/8/68); Foreign Policy and Congress; Bobby Kennedy (1/14/68)(Mar 14 1968); Civil Rights (3/14/68); Congressional Ethics (3/15/68)(Mar 15 1968); Gold (3/15/68); Rockefeller (Mar 22 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington Spotlight (3/21/68); Mar 21 1968)(Gold Crisis); Kennedy-Johnson struggle in Congress (Mar 22 1968) Congress: Civil rights, etc. (Mar 21 1968) Violin: the levers of power (3/29/68)(Mar.28 1968); Add to violin file (3/29/68)(Mar 29 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Tax Bill) (3/29/68)(Mar 29 1968)
  - Chronological files, 04/1968 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington Taxes (4/4/68); (04/04/1968) Johnson, politics, Congress (4/4/68)(04/04/191968) Periscope, Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (4/4/68); (Johnson's retirement)(04/ 4 1968) Biz,Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Taxes 4/12/68); (04/11/1968) (04/ 11, 1968)Nation Shaffer-hubbard (White House and; civil rights)(04/ 11 1968) Humphrey as V.P. the cover (04/ 16 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington, Taxes (4/25/68) Congress: gun curbs (4/25/68)(04/25/1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Query #1(4/26/68); (04/26/1968) Business, Nicholson and Copy desk from Shaffer (Biz 17; Taxes)(04/27/1968)
  - Chronological files, 05/01/1968-05/15/1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Poor People's March (5/2/68)-Exclusive (May 2 1968); Rocky (5/2/68)(May 2 1968); Add tax file (5/3/68)(May 3 1968); Query #11 of 5/1/68 (5/2/68(May 3 1968)(IRS wiretapping); Biz, Brink, Shaffer, Washington, Taxes (5/3/68)(May 3, 1968); Congressional reaction on March on Washington (5/9/68)(May 9 1968); Congressional reaction to Indiana primary (5/9/68)(May 9 1968); Biz, Brink, Shaffer, Washington, Taxes (5/9/68) (May 9 1968)
  - Chronological files, 05/16/1968-05/31/1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Crime in streets (5/16/68)(May 16, 1968); Add taxes (5/17/68)(May 17, 1968)N15 Congress; Query #1 on Democratic Doves (5/17/68)(May 17 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Taxes) (May 17, 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (The Tax fight)(5/16/68)(May 16 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Add Taxes 5/17/68)(May 17, 1968); Add Crime Bill (5/17/68)(May 17, 1968); Biz, Brink, Shaffer, Washington (Economics Load--taxes (5/23/68)(May 23 1968); Crime Bill (5/23/68)(May 23 1968) Truth-in-Lending (5/24/68)(May 24, 1968); Business-Brink,? from Sam Shaffer (Trade Spotlight)(May 28, 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Taxes 5/29/68) (May 29, 1968)
  - Chronological files, 06/1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Crime legislation (6/12/68)(Jun 6 1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington Query #8 on tax outlook (Jun 7 1968); Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (6/7/68)(Jun 7 1968)(Successor to Bob Kennedy's seat, departure ofThomas Kuchel); Steiger (6/13/68)(Jun 13 1968); Add to gun file (6/13/68)(Jun 13 1968); Biz, Brink, Martz, Shaffer, Newsweek (Gun Legislation)(6/13/68)(Jun '13 1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Guns (6/14/68)(Jun 14 1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Gun laws (6/14/68))(Jun 14 1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington,(6/14/68)(Excerpt from handout released by Sen. Harrison A.Williams); Guaranteed Income (6/20/68)(June 20 1968); Guns (6/20/68) (June 20 1968); Business, Martz from Shaffer (Add to tax file)(June 20, 1968); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington, Taxes (6.20/68)(Jun 20 1968); Institutional Gap (6/20/68 ) (Jun 21 1968); Gunsmoke (6/27/68) (Jun 28 1968); Supreme Court Fight (6/27/68 ) (Jun 27 1968); Biz, Brink, Shaffer, Washington (Metric System (6/28/68))(Jun 28 1968); Guns, (6/28/68) (Jun 28 1968); Add Supreme Court (6/28/68) (Jun 28 1968); Add Supreme Court fight (6/28/68); Add Supreme Court fight (6/28/68)
  - Chronological files, 07/01/1968-07/15/1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Cannon from Shaffer (The Convention System July 1 1968); Supreme Court fight (7/3/68) (Jul 3 1968); Add to court fight file (7/3/68) (Jul 3 1968); Congress (7/2/68) (Jul 4 1968); Subversive Activities Control Board (7/3/68)(Jul 4 1968); Congress (7/11/68); Supreme Court Fight (7/11/68) (Jul 11 1968)
  - Chronological files, 07/16/1968-07/31/1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week (7/18/68) (Jul 18 1968); Democratic Week (7/18/68 ) (Jul 18 1968); Teddy Kennedy (7/18/68 ) (Jul 18 1968); Add to platform story (Jul 19 1968); Republican Platform ( 7/19/68 ) (Jul 19 1968); No. 10 7/20/68; Iselin, Nation from Shaffer (Jul 20 1968); Query #10 on delegate count (Jul 24 1968); (Sen. Frank Carlson of Kansas) Congress Week (7/25/68 ) (Jul 25 1968); Add Congress file ( 7/26/68) (Jul 26 1968) Add Congress file (Jul 26 1968) GOP Platform (7/26/68)
  - Chronological files, 08/1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (8/1/68); The OOP Nominee (8/1/68)(Aug 1 1968)(Morton); GOP Convention Violin (8/8/68)(Nixon); Nation/Periscope Shaffer (Aug 14 1968)(Wallace Threat); McGovern (Aug 15 1968); Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Chicago Dem Platform (also; Political Lead)8/22/68; Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Chicago (8/23/68)(Add Platform); Nation, Iselin from Chicago, Shaffer-Milligan Minority Plank; Nation, Iselin, Shaffer,Chicago Platform (8/29/68); Nation, Iselin,Shaffer, Chicago For the violin (8/29/68)(Dem Convention)
  - Chronological files, 09/1968-10/20/1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Roundup (10/10/68); Correction No.3 10/12/68 Nation and Copy Desk from; Shaffer (N14 Debate Corr); Congress: New Faces (10/17/68)(Oct 17 1968); Nation and copy desk Shaffer/bishop (Congress)(Oct 19 1968); Violin (10/23/68)(Oct 23 1968) Honorable William V.Roth Jr.
  - Chronological files, 10/21/1968-10/31/1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington Rep. Roth (10/23/68); Query #5 of 10/23 (10/23)(Griffin); Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (10/24/68) (Telephone Conversation); Nation, Iselin Shaffer, Washington (10/24/68)(threnody); Query #1 (10/24/68)(Grover Hall); Cannon, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (Query #2 of 10/22(10/25/68); Cannon, Iselin, Gardner, Shaffer, Washington (your query; on Mel Laird (10/30/68)(President Nixon); Nation, Iselin, Auchinloss, Shaffer, Washington (Query; #13 (10/31/68)(Republican Leadership); Nation, Iselin, Shaffer, Washington (Electoral College deadlock (11/1/68)
  - Chronological files, 11/1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Nation, Iselin, Martz, Auchincloss, Shaffer, Washington(The Possibility of a Republican House as a result of a post-election switch(11/4/68); Martz from Shaffer Congress outlook (first report-9.45 p.m. Martz from Shaffer Second Congress Report (10.45 p.m.) Martz from Shaffer Third Congress Report (11.15) Martz from Shaffer Fourth Congress Report (11.35) Martz from Shaffer Fifth Congress Report (midnight) Martz from Shaffer and Simmons--Congress Outlook sixth; report: 12.30 a.m.; 13-Cong-Shaffer; 14-Cong-Shaffer; 15-Cong-Shaffer; Martz from Shaffer--Cong. roundup-eighth report 1.30 a.m. Martz from Shaffer--Cong. roundup-ninth report (2.30 a.m.); Martz from Shaffer-Cong. roundup-10th report (3 a.m.); Martz from Shaffer-Cong. roundup-eleventh report (3.40 a.m. The next Congress (11/7/68); The Democrats and the next President; Periscope from Shaffer 11-15 (Transition)(Nixon) Iselin from Shaffer (Nixon) Melfin (Shaffer); The nuclear proliferation treaty
  - Chronological files, 12/1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (The foreign policy fight)(Dec 5 1968); Scoop Jackson (12/5/68); Nation/Iselin/Periscope from Shaffer (Scoop Jackson); Cover--reaction (Dec 12 1968); Laird (12/12/68); Nation/Zick from Shaffer (Mansfield); Nation, Iselin, Zick, Shaffer, Washington (12/13/68); (Fulbright) Add to earlier files dealing with national commitments; debate, cabinet choices, etc (Dec 13 1968) Corrections (Dec 14 1968)(N18 Cover Tape)
  - Chronological files, 01/01/1969-01/06/1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Query #9 (Adam Powell)(01/1969); The 91st Congress (1/2/69)(Jan 2 1969); Hugh Scott (1/3/69)(Jan 3 1969); Kennedy (1/3/69)(Jan 3 1969); Kennedy (1/3/69) Take 2 (Jan 3 - 1969); Correction (1/4/69) (N17 Teddy); LBJ (.1/9/69) (Jan 9 1969); The Case of "the faith;ess elector" (Jan 9 1969)(Jordan); Gene McCarthy (Jan 10 1969); Elliot Richardson (1/10/69)(Jan 16 1969); With Cover-Nixon-Congress honeymoon; Filibuster (1/16/68)(Jan 16 1969); Congress Week (1/23/69)(Jan 23 1969); With Violin (1/23/69)(Jan 24 1969); Press, Smith, Nation, Shaffer, Washington (Add Nixon-Frank Shakespeare (1/29/69)(Jan 30 1969); For Violin-Nixon's encounter with the Congressional leaders (1/30/69)(Jan 30 1969)
  - Chronological files, 02/1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Finch (Feb 1 1969); Congress and the military-industrial complex (2/6/69)(Feb 6 1969); Postal Reform (2/6/69)(Feb 6 1969) Add to post office reform story (Feb 7 1969) Add Postoffice (2/7/69)(Feb 7 1969) 2/8/69; Nation and Copy Desk from Shaffer/Defrank Wash (Corrections)(Feb 8 1969)(N15 Missiles); With Cover - taxes ( 2/13/69)(Feb 13 1969) Hunger (1/20/69)(Feb 20 1969); One-bank holding companies (2/21/69)(Feb 21 1969) Query #2 (2/27/69)(Feb.27 1969)(Anti-ABM Sentiment); Spiro Agnew (2/27/69)(Feb 27 1969) FBI and Students (Feb 27 1969) Telephoner to Bishop (2/28/69)(Feb 28 1969)
  - Chronological files, 03/1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Juvenile Delinquency Investigation (3/6/69)(Mar 6 1969); ABM (3/7/69)(Mar 7 1969); Violin (3/7/69)(Mar 7 1969); Correction (3/8/69)(Nil Juvenile); Cities, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (The Cities' spokesman in Congress (3/19/69)(Mar 19 1969); Ribicoff Violin (3/20/69)(Mar 20 1969)(ABM); Cover (Mar 21 1969)(Goldwater); Add Cover (Mar 21 1969)(Conyers); Cities, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Mar 21 1969)(Javitts) Laird (3/21/69)(Mar 21 1969); Cities, Martz, Shaffer, Washington (Cities spokesman query) (Mar 25 1969); Violin (3/27/69)(Mar 27 1969)(American casualty rate in Vietnam); Obscenity (3/27)(Mar 27 1969)
  - Chronological files, 04/1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] To Publicity from Shaffer--(3/27)(Shaffer Meet the Press Mansfield)(Mar 27 1969); Sam Houston Johnson (4/3/69)(04/3/1969); Correction (4/3/69)(My No.24 of today: Sam Houston Johnson 04/3/1969); Violin-Neo-Isolationism (04/3/1969); Add violin (3/4/69)(04/4/1969)(ABM system); Cover Story (Pornographic material)(04/4/1969); Violin--Nixon's Domestic Program (04/10/1969); Teddy Kennedy (4/10/69)(04/101969); Correction (4/12/69)(N13 Teddy)(04/12/1969); Flying Pueblo file (4/17/69)(04/ 17 1969); "Flying Pueblo"--Congressional response (4/17/1969); Add Flying Pueblo file (4/18/69)(04/18/1969); Violin--Congressional reaction (4/17/69)(04/18/1969); Correction (4/18/69) KLEIN and Copy Desk from Shaffer/; De Frank (N18 Cover Tape) Education Shaffer, Washington-Cover (4/25/69) (Sen.Ribicoff); Congress Week-- the challenge to Nixon (4/24/69)(04/24/1969); Correction (4/26/69)(N18 Congress)(04/26/1969)
  - Chronological files, 05/01/1969-05/15/1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] 100 Days-Congress (May 1 1969); Dirksen and Nixon- -- Take Two (5/1/69) (May 1 1969); ABM (5/2/69) (May 2 1969); ABM (5/2/69) -Take One ABM (May 2 1969); Fortas (5/8/69) -Congress (May 8 1969); Query #7 (May 9 1969) (Fortas); Query #2 (May 9 1969) (Mitchell: Fortas); Fortas (May 10 1969); Add Fortas file 5-10-69 (May 10 1969); Fortas Congress -- Take Two (May 15 1969)
  - Chronological files, 05/l6/1969-05/31/1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Draft (5/16/69) (May 16 1969); Fortas -- Take 6 (5/16/69) (May 16 1969); Anti-military complex (5/22/69) (May 22 1969); City Riots Report (Exclusive) 5/29/69; No.26 5/30/69 Nation, Martin from Shaffer (Teddy Kennedy); Correction (5/31/69) (N17 Congress)
  - Chronological files, 06/1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Dwight Martin (Nation) from Shaffer (6/5/69) (Jun 5 1969); (Dirksen)OEO (6/5/69) (Jun«5 1969) Violin (6/5/69) (Jun 5 1969) (Nixon) Vietnam-Congress (6/12/69) (Jun 12 1969); Correction (6/14/69 ) (N17 violin tape five) Powell (6/19/69) (Jun 19 1969) Violin (6/19/69) (Jun 19 1969) Query #10 - taxes (Jun 20 1969) Further add tax file (6/20/69 ) (Jun 20 1969) N15 Supreme Court (Jun 21 1969) Add taxes (6/26/69) Publicity from Shaffer 6/26/69 (Shaffer-Face the Nation,Ford); Taxes (6/26/69 ) (Jun 26 1969); National Commitments Resolution ( 6/26/69 ) (Jun 26 1969); Knowles (view from Senate) (Jun 27 1969) (Dirksen) Correction (Biz 17 LEDE)(Jun 28 1969)
  - Chronological files, 07/01/1969-07/17/1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Taxes-Take II (outlook)(Jul 2 1969); Congress (Take III)(7/2/69)(Jul 2 1969); Congress (7/3/69)(Jul 3 1969); ABM (7/10/69)(Jul 10 1969); Republican rebellion (7/10/69)(Jul 10 1969); ABM-Take Two (7/10/69)(Jul 10 1969); Taxes (7/ll/69)(Jul 11 1969); Correction (Jul 12 1969)(N12 Debate); Taxes (7/17/69(Jul 17 1969); ABM (7/17/69)(Jul 17 1969)
  - Chronological files, 07/18/1969-07/31/1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Add taxes (7/18/69)(Jul 18 1969); Kennedy (Jul 19 1969) Surtax (7/24/69)(Jul 24 1969); Kennedy-Take II (Congress)(Jul 24 1969); The Nixon Trip (7/25/69)(Jul 25 1969); Kennedy (7/25/69)(Jul 25 1969); Kennedy-7/26 (Jul 26 1969); Politics: 1972 (7/31/69)(Jul 31 1969); Surtax (7/31/69)(Jul 31 1969); Add taxes
  - Chronological files, 08/1969-09/1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Correction (Aug 2, 1969) Business and Copydesk from; Shaffer Week (Biz 17 Tax Tape Two Final Para); ABM (8/7/69)(Aug 7 1969)(Take I and II); Smith Sidebar to ABM story (8/8/69)(Aug 8 1969); Add Smith Sidebar (Aug 8 1969); The Nixon Doctrine (8/8/69)(Aug 8 1969); Correction (8/19/69)(N15 Maggie); Haynesworth (8/20/69)(Aug 20 1969); Mitchell cover (8/20/69)(Aug 20 1969); Pete Callaway from Shaffer, Washington (8/27/69); Mitchell (8/27/69)(Aug 27 1969)
  - Chronological files, 10/1969 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Haynsworth (9/9/69)(0ct 9 1969); Add Haynsworth (Oct 10 1969); Nixon Message to Congress (10/9/69)(Oct 10 1969); Correction (10/11/69)(N15 Haynesworth); With Vietnam Cover (9/10/69)(Oct 10 1969); Add Viet file (10/9/69)(Oct 10 1969); Haynsworth (Congress)(Oct 15 1969); Moratorium (Take I)--Congress (10/15/69) (Oct 15 1969); Violin (Vietnam), 10/23/69 (Oct 23 1969); Agnew (Take III)(Oct 23 1969); Nixon-Haynsworth (Take III)(Oct 23 1969); Los Angeles from Washington (Shaffer) --10/24/69); (Oct 24 1969)(Tom Kuchel) Lindsay Cover (10/24/69)(Oct 24 1969); Congress (10/30/69)
  - Chronological files, 11/01/1969-11/15/1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Agnew-Congress view Take I (Nov 6 1969); Haynsworth (11/6/69)(Nov.6 1969); Violin (Vietnam) -11/6/69 (Nov 6 1969); Add Violin (11/7/69); Add Haynsworth (11/7/69); Correction (11/8/69)(N22 Violin); Draft reform (11/13/69); Draft; Draft (Draft reform); Haynsworth (11/3/69)(Nov 13 1969); Violin (11/14/69)(Nov 14 1969); Haynsworth (11/14/69)(Nov 14 1969); Haynsworth-Dent (Nov 15 1969)